{
    "id": "19_Health_228",
    "claim": "Scientists from the Universidad Nacional Autonoma de Mexico reported the results of their most recent research, with which they demonstrated that the ingestion of a bell, between an hour and a half hour before sexual intercourse, not only improves the performance of the male, but increases his resistance and the duration of erections. 'The particular combination of ingredients has a positive impact on the production of testosterone and adrenaline, which, combined, create a really remarkable effect on the male, regardless of age ', said Professor Morbonio Guiño Codazo, responsible for the study. In the experiments, the subjects managed to maintain relationships for more than six hours in a row, without showing any signs of exhaustion. And best of all, there were no side effects or adverse reactions. The results of the study caused the main bakeries of the country and surrounding neighborhoods to begin to increase the production of campechanas, but it is feared that in a matter of hours there will be a shortage of coveted bread. It should be noted that Professor Codazo's group has also achieved excellent results with chilindrinas in improving female sexual performance, but the tests in this section are still in preliminary phase. I'm sorry.",
    "source": "www.eldizque.com",
    "date": "05/12/2016",
    "veracity": 0,
    "claims": [
        {
            "claim": "Scientists from the Universidad Nacional Autonoma de Mexico reported the results of their most recent research, with which they demonstrated that the ingestion of a bell, between an hour and a half hour before sexual intercourse, not only improves the performance of the male, but increases his resistance and the duration of erections.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Where did Scientists report the results of their most recent research?",
                    "answer": "Universidad Nacional Autonoma de Mexico"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How does ingesting a bell improve the performance of a male?",
                    "score": 0.8636,
                    "answers": "with which they demonstrated that the ingestion of a bell , between an hour and a half hour before sexual intercourse , not only improves the performance of the male , but increases his resistance and the duration of erections|relcl\tthe male|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Did scientists from the Universidad Nacional Autonoma de Mexico report the results of their most recent research?",
                    "score": 0.859,
                    "answers": "de Mexico|prep\tmost recent|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did the scientists say about ingesting a bell before sexual intercourse?",
                    "score": 0.8336,
                    "answers": "www.eldizque.com|nsubj\tthat Scientists from the Universidad Nacional Autonoma de Mexico reported the results of their most recent research , with which they demonstrated that the ingestion of a bell , between an hour and a half hour before sexual intercourse , not only improves the performance of the male , but increases his resistance and the duration of erections|ccomp\tthe results of their most recent research , with which they demonstrated that the ingestion of a bell , between an hour and a half hour before sexual intercourse , not only improves the performance of the male , but increases his resistance and the duration of erections|dobj\ttheir most recent research , with which they demonstrated that the ingestion of a bell , between an hour and a half hour before sexual intercourse , not only improves the performance of the male , but increases his resistance and the duration of erections|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the effects of ingesting a bell?",
                    "score": 0.7674,
                    "answers": "erections|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between ingesting a bell and sexual intercourse?",
                    "score": 0.7183,
                    "answers": "sexual|amod\tsexual intercourse|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "'The particular combination of ingredients has a positive impact on the production of testosterone and adrenaline, which, combined, create a really remarkable effect on the male, regardless of age ', said Professor Morbonio Guiño Codazo, responsible for the study.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What was the age of the male?",
                    "answer": "age"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What effects does combining ingredients have on the production of testosterone and adrenaline have on a man?",
                    "score": 0.8957,
                    "answers": "a really remarkable effect on the male|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What ingredients are used to produce testosterone and adrenaline?",
                    "score": 0.8809,
                    "answers": "of ingredients|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What age group does Professor Morbonio Guiño Codazo work for?",
                    "score": 0.8315,
                    "answers": "regardless of age|advmod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between testosterone and adrenaline?",
                    "score": 0.768,
                    "answers": "of testosterone and adrenaline , which , combined , create a really remarkable effect on the male , regardless of age|prep\ttestosterone and adrenaline , which , combined , create a really remarkable effect on the male , regardless of age|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "In the experiments, the subjects managed to maintain relationships for more than six hours in a row, without showing any signs of exhaustion.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "How many hours in a row were the subjects able to maintain relationships?",
                    "answer": "six hours"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How long did the experiments last?",
                    "score": 0.8385,
                    "answers": "www.eldizque.com reported on 05/12/2016 that In the experiments , the subjects managed to maintain relationships for more than six hours in a row , without showing any signs of exhaustion|ROOT\ton 05/12/2016|prep\tthe experiments|pobj\tthat In the experiments , the subjects managed to maintain relationships for more than six hours in a row , without showing any signs of exhaustion|ccomp\tto maintain relationships for more than six hours in a row , without showing any signs of exhaustion|xcomp\tfor more than six hours in a row|prep\tmore than six|nummod\tmore than six hours in a row|pobj\tin a row|prep\ta row|pobj\twithout showing any signs of exhaustion|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many hours of sleep did the subjects have during the experiments?",
                    "score": 0.8242,
                    "answers": "www.eldizque.com|nsubj\tthat|mark\tthe|det\t,|punct\tthe|det\tthe subjects|nsubj\tto|aux\tmore|amod\tthan|quantmod\ta|det\t,|punct\tshowing any signs of exhaustion|pcomp\tany|det\tof exhaustion|prep\texhaustion|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the relationship between the subjects in the experiments?",
                    "score": 0.7863,
                    "answers": "relationships|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the evidence of exhaustion in the experiments conducted by the researchers?",
                    "score": 0.7299,
                    "answers": "any signs of exhaustion|dobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "And best of all, there were no side effects or adverse reactions.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "How many side effects were there?",
                    "answer": "no side effects or adverse reactions"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What are the side effects of adverse reactions?",
                    "score": 0.9008,
                    "answers": "of all|prep\tadverse|amod\tadverse reactions|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many side effects or adverse reactions were reported in 2016?",
                    "score": 0.8709,
                    "answers": "www.eldizque.com reported on 05/12/2016 that And best of all , there were no side effects or adverse reactions|ROOT"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The results of the study caused the main bakeries of the country and surrounding neighborhoods to begin to increase the production of campechanas, but it is feared that in a matter of hours there will be a shortage of coveted bread.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the fear of the increase in production of campechanas?",
                    "answer": "in a matter of hours there will be a shortage of coveted bread"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How long did it take to produce campechanas?",
                    "score": 0.7985,
                    "answers": "in a matter of hours|prep\tof hours|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did the study say about the shortage of coveted bread?",
                    "score": 0.7498,
                    "answers": "it is feared that in a matter of hours there will be a shortage of coveted bread|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the production of campechanas?",
                    "score": 0.7369,
                    "answers": "the main bakeries of the country and surrounding neighborhoods to begin to increase the production of campechanas|ccomp\tto increase the production of campechanas|xcomp\tthe production of campechanas|dobj\tof campechanas|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of campechanas production?",
                    "score": 0.7114,
                    "answers": "campechanas|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "It should be noted that Professor Codazo's group has also achieved excellent results with chilindrinas in improving female sexual performance, but the tests in this section are still in preliminary phase.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.eldizque.com report that Professor Codazo's group achieved excellent results with chilindrinas?",
                    "answer": "05/12/2016"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What has Professor Codazo done with chilindrinas in improving female sexual performance?",
                    "score": 0.8525,
                    "answers": "that It should be noted that Professor Codazo 's group has also achieved excellent results with chilindrinas in improving female sexual performance , but the tests in this section are still in preliminary phase|ccomp\tProfessor Codazo 's|poss"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What has Codazo done with chilindrinas?",
                    "score": 0.8135,
                    "answers": "Professor Codazo 's group|nsubj\texcellent results with chilindrinas|dobj\twith chilindrinas|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many chilindrinas has Professor Codazo performed?",
                    "score": 0.8097,
                    "answers": "www.eldizque.com|nsubj\twww.eldizque.com reported on 05/12/2016 that It should be noted that Professor Codazo 's group has also achieved excellent results with chilindrinas in improving female sexual performance , but the tests in this section are still in preliminary phase|ROOT\ton 05/12/2016|prep\t's|case\tfemale|amod\tthe tests in this section|nsubj\tthis section|pobj\tthe tests in this section are still in preliminary phase|conj\tin preliminary phase|prep\tpreliminary phase|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the chilindrinas?",
                    "score": 0.7006,
                    "answers": "chilindrinas|pobj"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}